let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Divided by zero is?",
    answer: "Run time Error",
    options: [
      "Syntax Error",
      "Run time Error",
      "System Error",
      "Output Error"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What can be used to create the objects?",
    answer: "class",
    options: [
      "objects",
      "module",
      "data item",
      "class"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A Program must never be?",
    answer: "long",
    options: [
      "Understandable",
      "accurate",
      "long",
      "portable"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " An array is the collection of?",
    answer: "Both",
    options: [
      "Common Namee",
      "Common Datatype",
      "Both",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Debugging is the technique for?",
    answer: "remove errors from code",
    options: [
      "remove errors from code",
      "edit software",
      "developing software",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
   {
   numb: 6,
   question: " What is not true about java language?",
    answer: "It is platform dependent",
     options: [
      "It is platform independent",
	  "It is platform dependent",
      "It is object oriented",
      "It is robust and secure"
    ]
  },
  {
   numb: 7,
   question: " Java uses?",
    answer: "Assembler",
     options: [
      "Compiler",
	  "Interpreter",
      "Both 1 and 2",
      "Assembler"
    ]
  },
   {
   numb: 8,
   question: " For compiling process java used?",
    answer: "javac",
     options: [
      "javac",
      "javacomp",
      "java",
      "jdb"
    ]
  },
  {
   numb: 9,
   question: "For interpreting process java used?",
    answer: "java",
     options: [
      "javac",
      "javacomp",
      "java",
      "jdb"
    ]
  },
  {
   numb: 10,
   question: " For viewing web application java uses?",
    answer: "applet viewer",
     options: [
      "applet viewer",
      "javacomp",
      "jdb",
      "javac"
    ]
  },
];